
 const resData=[
  {
    accordion: "Furlong Painting Contractor Induction Program",
    children: [
        { name: "Introduction Program", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd02a3dd33a12e46098c2004068c6c917b?mode=embed" },
    { name: "History and Mission", url: "asdasd" },
    { name: "Interpretative Statements", url: "asdasd" },
    { name: "Contractor Standards and Expectations", url: "asdasd" },
    { name: "Personal and Business Documents", url: "asdasd" }

],
  },
  {
    accordion: "Module 1 - Human Resources",
    children: [
        { name: "Conditions of Engagement", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd02a3dd33a12e46098c2004068c6c917b?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Code of Conduct", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhde2a15a2eaf744bb6ad06191d3c52936a?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Duty of Care", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd909b6a4c4b7941959a01e9681f2ba549?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Suitability for Work", url:" " },
        { name: "Fatigue Management", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd6bdb7d00900d47f69d0ae51354d4f6f7?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Bullying, Harassment, Violence, Aggressive and inappropriate Behaviour ", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd19dae3f0ff1449d59d671485126d9b8c?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Incident Reporting", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd6d806473ebe1408d95e295034c0e4bc7?mode=embed" },
        { name: "QUIZ - Module 1", quiz:{
   
          totalQuestions: 7,
          perQuestionScore: 1,
          questions: [
              {  
                question:"Do you fully understand and are prepared to abide by the Contractors Conditions of Engagement?",
                choices:["Yes","No"],
              correctAnswer:"Yes",
              questionNumber:1
                },
                {  
                  question:"Who is responsible for complying with the Contractor Code of Conduct?",
                  choices:["All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting",
                "Only Furlong Painting Employees",
                "Only Furlong Painting Contractors",
                ],
                correctAnswer: 'All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting',
                questionNumber:2
        
                  },
                  {  
                    question:"The Occupational Health and Safety Act requires Employers to provide a safe workplace. Each contractor and their employees / sub contractors are required to....",
                    choices:[
                  "Follow only the client's safety processes",
                  "Make sure someone on site is fit to perform nominated duties.",
                  "Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                  
                ],
                correctAnswer:"Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                questionNumber:3,
                    },
                    {  
                      question:"What is the expected criteria for workplace presentation?",
                      choices:[
                   "Workwear to be clean and, where possible, bearing the Furlong painting logo",
                   "Contractors to be well rested and not under the influence of a substance that might impair the ability to perform required tasks safely",
                   "That all electrical equipment to be have a valid test and tag",
                   "All of the above",
                    
                  ],
                  correctAnswer:"All of the above",
                  questionNumber:4
                      },
                      {  
                        question:"What is deemed to be workplace bullying?",
                        choices:[
                      "When more than two people agree that comments are inappropriate",
                      "Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                      "Where Furlong Painting stops offering my business work opportunities",
                      
                    ],
                    correctAnswer:"Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                    questionNumber:5
                        },
                        {  
                          question:"What best describes why Workplace Fatigue Management is an important part of the Risk Management Program?",
                          choices:[
                        "It may affect safety in the workplace",,
                        "It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                        "It gives me an excuse to sleep in every day",,
                        
                      ],
                      correctAnswer:"It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                      questionNumber:6
                          },
                          {  
                            question:"Which of the following MUST be reported immediately to company management?",
                            choices:[
                          "An injury",
                          "Property Damage",
                          "All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                          
                        ],
                        correctAnswer:"All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                        questionNumber:7
                            },
            ]
         
        }}
],
  },
  {
    accordion: "Module 2 - Workplace Health, Safety and Wellbeing",
    children: [
        { name: "On-Site Works Process", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd7dd2947937024226892b4e2b3a61dcf1?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Safe Work Method Statement", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd8d499033ba4448bba0460263dec7a7b0?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Stop Work", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd2e5e6f7cd47240e4a69af0f674ab1735?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Personal Protective Equipment", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd6bdbce39f84e4ec9a3116fd8cf8b27b2?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Manual Handling", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhdc03ff34b46d643928835df18831a806e?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Working at Heights", url: "asdhttps://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd77a0350bd3704dcf8c816c4f469e3d5e?mode=embedasd" },
        { name: "Electrical", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd3aee4c2236134092b3605c5b86277614?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Confined Spaces", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd716bf702f1fd4eca87bd193d280128f4?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Housekeeping- Slips, Trips and Falls", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd3ec39f97ae444b428cdc5a0d11d8dff0?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Driver Safety", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhda061c8a050fe4308a2eafaf296f209b9?mode=embed" },
        { name: "QUIZ - Module 2", quiz: {
   
          totalQuestions: 7,
          perQuestionScore: 1,
          questions: [
              {  
                question:"Do you fully understand and are prepared to abide by the Contractors Conditions of Engagement(Test 2)?",
                choices:["Yes","No"],
              correctAnswer:"Yes",
              questionNumber:1
                },
                {  
                  question:"Who is responsible for complying with the Contractor Code of Conduct?",
                  choices:["All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting",
                "Only Furlong Painting Employees",
                "Only Furlong Painting Contractors",
                ],
                correctAnswer: 'All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting',
                questionNumber:2
        
                  },
                  {  
                    question:"The Occupational Health and Safety Act requires Employers to provide a safe workplace. Each contractor and their employees / sub contractors are required to....",
                    choices:[
                  "Follow only the client's safety processes",
                  "Make sure someone on site is fit to perform nominated duties.",
                  "Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                  
                ],
                correctAnswer:"Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                questionNumber:3,
                    },
                    {  
                      question:"What is the expected criteria for workplace presentation?",
                      choices:[
                   "Workwear to be clean and, where possible, bearing the Furlong painting logo",
                   "Contractors to be well rested and not under the influence of a substance that might impair the ability to perform required tasks safely",
                   "That all electrical equipment to be have a valid test and tag",
                   "All of the above",
                    
                  ],
                  correctAnswer:"All of the above",
                  questionNumber:4
                      },
                      {  
                        question:"What is deemed to be workplace bullying?",
                        choices:[
                      "When more than two people agree that comments are inappropriate",
                      "Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                      "Where Furlong Painting stops offering my business work opportunities",
                      
                    ],
                    correctAnswer:"Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                    questionNumber:5
                        },
                        {  
                          question:"What best describes why Workplace Fatigue Management is an important part of the Risk Management Program?",
                          choices:[
                        "It may affect safety in the workplace",,
                        "It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                        "It gives me an excuse to sleep in every day",,
                        
                      ],
                      correctAnswer:"It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                      questionNumber:6
                          },
                          {  
                            question:"Which of the following MUST be reported immediately to company management?",
                            choices:[
                          "An injury",
                          "Property Damage",
                          "All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                          
                        ],
                        correctAnswer:"All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                        questionNumber:7
                            },
            ]
         
        } },
    ],
  },
  {
    accordion: "Module 3 - Workplace",
    children: [
        { name: "Dangerous / Hazardous Goods", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhdce05a65426d2440d8f5b5554adbf7c35?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Lead", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd9c2218eb8a13474cabe40dad9b29991d?mode=embed" },
        { name: "Asbestos", url: "https://writer.zohopublic.com/writer/published/0byhd7c6f53db5f884fbabbd1d91c0317df9c?mode=embed" },
        { name: "QUIZ - Module 3", quiz: {
   
          totalQuestions: 7,
          perQuestionScore: 1,
          questions: [
              {  
                question:"Do you fully understand and are prepared to abide by the Contractors Conditions of Engagement?",
                choices:["Yes","No"],
              correctAnswer:"Yes",
              questionNumber:1
                },
                {  
                  question:"Who is responsible for complying with the Contractor Code of Conduct?",
                  choices:["All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting",
                "Only Furlong Painting Employees",
                "Only Furlong Painting Contractors",
                ],
                correctAnswer: 'All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting',
                questionNumber:2
        
                  },
                  {  
                    question:"The Occupational Health and Safety Act requires Employers to provide a safe workplace. Each contractor and their employees / sub contractors are required to....",
                    choices:[
                  "Follow only the client's safety processes",
                  "Make sure someone on site is fit to perform nominated duties.",
                  "Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                  
                ],
                correctAnswer:"Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                questionNumber:3,
                    },
                    {  
                      question:"What is the expected criteria for workplace presentation?",
                      choices:[
                   "Workwear to be clean and, where possible, bearing the Furlong painting logo",
                   "Contractors to be well rested and not under the influence of a substance that might impair the ability to perform required tasks safely",
                   "That all electrical equipment to be have a valid test and tag",
                   "All of the above",
                    
                  ],
                  correctAnswer:"All of the above",
                  questionNumber:4
                      },
                      {  
                        question:"What is deemed to be workplace bullying?",
                        choices:[
                      "When more than two people agree that comments are inappropriate",
                      "Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                      "Where Furlong Painting stops offering my business work opportunities",
                      
                    ],
                    correctAnswer:"Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                    questionNumber:5
                        },
                        {  
                          question:"What best describes why Workplace Fatigue Management is an important part of the Risk Management Program?",
                          choices:[
                        "It may affect safety in the workplace",,
                        "It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                        "It gives me an excuse to sleep in every day",,
                        
                      ],
                      correctAnswer:"It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                      questionNumber:6
                          },
                          {  
                            question:"Which of the following MUST be reported immediately to company management?",
                            choices:[
                          "An injury",
                          "Property Damage",
                          "All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                          
                        ],
                        correctAnswer:"All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                        questionNumber:7
                            },
            ]
         
        }},
    ],
  },
  {
    accordion: "Module 4 – Environmental",
    children: [
        { name: "Company Environment Objective", url: "https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vT1EFSDwjq2Sl-JkBLhfGnvMKLLx3JaAhMY86eQDAHTNrsqiq9mg1nYY-4DKa5EU6eP_4NJEYduG-Ix/pub?embedded=true" },
        { name: "Waste Management", url: "https://docs.google.com/document/d/e/2PACX-1vT1EFSDwjq2Sl-JkBLhfGnvMKLLx3JaAhMY86eQDAHTNrsqiq9mg1nYY-4DKa5EU6eP_4NJEYduG-Ix/pub?embedded=true" },
        { name: "QUIZ : Module 4", quiz: {
   
          totalQuestions: 7,
          perQuestionScore: 1,
          questions: [
              {  
                question:"Do you fully understand and are prepared to abide by the Contractors Conditions of Engagement?",
                choices:["Yes","No"],
              correctAnswer:"Yes",
              questionNumber:1
                },
                {  
                  question:"Who is responsible for complying with the Contractor Code of Conduct?",
                  choices:["All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting",
                "Only Furlong Painting Employees",
                "Only Furlong Painting Contractors",
                ],
                correctAnswer: 'All persons performing work on behalf of Furlong Painting',
                questionNumber:2
        
                  },
                  {  
                    question:"The Occupational Health and Safety Act requires Employers to provide a safe workplace. Each contractor and their employees / sub contractors are required to....",
                    choices:[
                  "Follow only the client's safety processes",
                  "Make sure someone on site is fit to perform nominated duties.",
                  "Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                  
                ],
                correctAnswer:"Ensure compliance with both legislative requirements and Furlong Painting risk management policies/procedures.",
                questionNumber:3,
                    },
                    {  
                      question:"What is the expected criteria for workplace presentation?",
                      choices:[
                   "Workwear to be clean and, where possible, bearing the Furlong painting logo",
                   "Contractors to be well rested and not under the influence of a substance that might impair the ability to perform required tasks safely",
                   "That all electrical equipment to be have a valid test and tag",
                   "All of the above",
                    
                  ],
                  correctAnswer:"All of the above",
                  questionNumber:4
                      },
                      {  
                        question:"What is deemed to be workplace bullying?",
                        choices:[
                      "When more than two people agree that comments are inappropriate",
                      "Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                      "Where Furlong Painting stops offering my business work opportunities",
                      
                    ],
                    correctAnswer:"Repeated and unwanted negative behaviour, relating to gender, sexuality, cultural background etc",
                    questionNumber:5
                        },
                        {  
                          question:"What best describes why Workplace Fatigue Management is an important part of the Risk Management Program?",
                          choices:[
                        "It may affect safety in the workplace",,
                        "It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                        "It gives me an excuse to sleep in every day",,
                        
                      ],
                      correctAnswer:"It highlights the signs and symptoms of fatigue which helps to minimise the risks associated in the workplace",
                      questionNumber:6
                          },
                          {  
                            question:"Which of the following MUST be reported immediately to company management?",
                            choices:[
                          "An injury",
                          "Property Damage",
                          "All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                          
                        ],
                        correctAnswer:"All incidents – injury, near miss, hazard reporting, environmental issue, property damage / loss.",
                        questionNumber:7
                            },
            ]
         
        }},
        { name: "Acceptance", url: "" },
    ],
  },
 
]; 

// const quizQuestion=[
//   {
//     question:"",
//     answer:[
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     question:"",
//     answer:[
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     question:"",
//     answer:[
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     question:"",
//     answer:[
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     question:"",
//     answer:[
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//     ]
//   },
//   {
//     question:"",
//     answer:[
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//       {text:"",correct:false},
//     ]
//   },
  
// ]


export default resData